// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Find the letter 'V'",
    answer: "V",
    options: [
      "Z",
      "A",
      "V",
      "N"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Find the letter 'N'",
    answer: "N",
    options: [
      "M",
      "N",
      "X",
      "K"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'Y' ",
    answer: "y",
    options: [
      "v",
      "y",
      "r",
      "a"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'Q' ",
    answer: "q",
    options: [
      "s",
      "l",
      "q",
      "h"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Select correct lowercase letter 'J' ",
    answer: "j",
    options: [
      "i",
      "s",
      "v",
      "j"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'd' ",
    answer: "D",
    options: [
      "Z",
      "B",
      "D",
      "T"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'n' ",
    answer: "N",
    options: [
      "M",
      "N",
      "X",
      "K"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'r' ",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "V",
      "R",
      "W",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the letter 'C'",
    answer: "C",
    options: [
      "A",
      "Y",
      "C",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Find the letter 'X'",
    answer: "X",
    options: [
      "V",
      "X",
      "A",
      "U"
    ]
  }
  
];
